{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Take an umbrella with you ___ it should rain.",
      "a": "in time",
      "b": "in case",
      "c": "unless",
      "d": "even if",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- In case: as a way of being safe from something that might happen or might be true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Matt was absent from school yesterday ___.",
      "a": "because his fever",
      "b": "because of he had a fever",
      "c": "because he had a fever",
      "d": "because with a fever",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Because: used when you are giving the reason for something ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "They seem to eat well;___ they always look hungry.",
      "a": "except",
      "b": "until",
      "c": "nevertheless",
      "d": "unless",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Nevertheless: in spite of a fact that you have just mentioned",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kitty studied all afternoon. She was ___ studying that she couldn't go to the restaurant with us.",
      "a": "so busy",
      "b": "very busy",
      "c": "too busy",
      "d": "much busy",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- So...that: shows the result of something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "As you treat me, ___ will I treat you.",
      "a": "and",
      "b": "like",
      "c": "as",
      "d": "so",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- So: used to say that someone does something because of the reason just stated",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mr. Chung came to work today ___ he sprained his ankle last night.",
      "a": "unless",
      "b": "despite",
      "c": "although",
      "d": "because",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Although: used to introduce a statement that makes your main statement seem surprising or unlikely [= though]",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ grammar is concerned, there is nothing to be desired in this composition.",
      "a": "So far as",
      "b": "So that",
      "c": "According as",
      "d": "As well as",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- So far as: to the extent of",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duncan will accept the post ___ the salary is satisfactory.",
      "a": "unless",
      "b": "though",
      "c": "on condition that",
      "d": "for fear that",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- On condition that: provided that\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Most writers speak of their fame ___ it were quite a worthless matter.",
      "a": "al though",
      "b": "as if",
      "c": "according as",
      "d": "so far as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- As if:  in a way that makes it seem that something is true or that something is happening\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is said to have won the first prize, but I doubt ___ it is true.",
      "a": "when",
      "b": "what",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "whether",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Whether: used when talking about a choice you have to make or about something that is not certain",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}